[Episode 9]
It's okay, Yun. It's nothing, see?
I'm holding your hand.
Don't go anywhere, don't listen to anything,
just hold my hand tight. It's okay.
It's all right. It's nothing.
It's nothing, Yun.
Ma'am.
Because of you, some of us can't eat nor sleep.
I'm not some dog that comes and goes
when you say so, you jerk!
Mister.
What the...
Were you staying with Muhyeok this whole time?
What did I ever do to you to get yelled at?
What's wrong with you?
You're not acting like yourself!
- Where is Choi Yun?
- Is he in surgery?
- What happened?
- Where is he?
Are you all right?
Can you hear me?
- Please, just one comment.
- Just one comment.
Galchi!
Jump!
Isn't it pretty?
Galchi, what do you think?
Very pretty!
Yun! Yun!
It's me.
Sit down!
How did it go, doctor?
His heart may be damaged.
It says "together" in Korean.
We don't know how he got such a necklace.
But we're certain it must be
related to his birth mother.
Muhyeok.
Hey!
Mother!
Who do you think you are?
So-called manager... Where and what were you doing?
How could you let this happen to my baby?
Where were you the whole time?
Where were you, you bastard?
Cut it out. It's not Mr. Cha's fault. Stop it!
Calm down, Mother.
I hate this guy.
If he did his job properly,
this wouldn't have happened to Yun.
It's all this bastard's fault! It's all his fault!
Why are you blaming an innocent person?
You're too emotional right now. Calm down!
Sorry, Mr. Cha. Please be understanding.
If something happens to Yun, I won't forgive you!
I won't forgive you!
- Come inside!
- You won't get away with this!
I'm sorry. I'll apologize on her behalf.
Son! Yun! Mom is here.
Sorry, Yun. For coming late...
Yun. Yun!
I'm sorry for coming so late.
What am I going to do?
Yun!
Hello. How are you?
The results.
Ligaments in his right ankle and knee were damaged.
Fortunately, only one leg is damaged.
Once the cast is off, he'll have no problem walking.
The problem is his heart.
His heart?
According to his records,
Yun genetically has a very weak heart.
During the operation, an issue with his heart arose,
which extended the surgery.
We have to wait for further test results but
I think his chest hit the handle hard in the accident.
His heart may have developed a serious problem.
We need to stabilize him and monitor his progress.
Yun, Yun, are you awake?
Yun, are you awake?
Mom!
Yes, Mom is here! Mom is right here!
Eunchae!
What?
Where is Eunchae?
Eunchae is doing fine. It's fine.
Will you bring Eunchae?
Yun is looking for Eunchae. Please bring her.
Wait.
Have we met somewhere before?
I think his chest hit the handle hard in the accident.
His heart may have developed a serious problem.
I'm so furious...
That awful brat will put me in an early grave.
I know...
She hasn't slept or had a drop of water.
Does she want to live or die?
Even Yun's mom is eating something!
I know...
Is Yun your husband or something?
Are you gonna die if he does?
That's what I'm saying!
Fine. You grab her arms, you open her mouth!
Let's force feed her.
I won't have my child die over some guy.
Wait, wait. Just leave her be.
We can't force her to eat.
Yeah.
Who are you?
It's Yun's manager.
Where is Eunchae?
Where is she?
Eunchae. The sleaz... Yun's manager is here.
Eunchae hasn't drank any water,
hasn't had any sleep
and is almost showing symptoms of autism.
She's in a fragile state,
so don't talk too loudly.
And don't make her feel uneasy. Be careful.
Yun is awake.
He's awake?
Yun is alive?
He's looking for you.
Let's go. They want me to bring you.
Blockhead!
Yun's gonna die while waiting for you.
Let's go!
Mister! Put me down! Put me down!
Put me down, Mister!
- Eunchae.
- Mom!
Mister!
Leave them alone, Mom.
She's gotta go, even if it's like that.
Or else she might rot and die in that room.
- But still...
- He's so hot...
No, no!
What are you doing?
Put me down!
Put me down! What are you doing?
Mister!
What do you think you're doing?
I won't go! I said I'm not going!
I won't go!
Don't be angry. Don't yell.
I heard you didn't sleep and didn't drink.
Save your energy.
I'm not going to Yun. Do you hear me?
Listen up.
I'm not going to Yun.
I can't go...
Not after what I did to him.
I was so cruel to him.
How can I look him in the eyes?
That's a lot of tears for someone
who didn't drink any water.
Are you a kid?
You're going to flood the place. Stop crying!
If you keep crying, I'll just keep you, forever!
Let's eat. Let's eat something.
Stop the car.
Would you rather eat or kiss me?
Stop the car, now!
Would you rather eat or sleep with me?
I'm going to open the door and jump out!
Would you rather eat? Or just live with me?
Would you rather eat?
Or would you rather...
die with me?
[Let's eet]
Don't play with your food!
- Let's go.
- I don't want to go.
I want to stay here. I just want to stay next to Yun.
It's not going to be over in one or two days.
Go home, sleep, and pull yourself together.
Minju will look after him. Let's go.
But I should be there.
He needs his mom...
Yun... Son...
A mother needs to be by her child!
I have to be here for him.
Muhyeok!
Muhyeok! Muhyeok!
Who do you think you are?
Where and what were you doing?
If he did his job properly,
this wouldn't have happened to Yun.
It's all this bastard's fault! It's all his fault!
If something happens to Yun, I won't forgive you!
- Come inside!
- You won't get away with this!
What room is Choi Yun in?
Just a moment.
You'll have to go to Internal Medicine.
Okay.
Come in.
What took you so long?
Yun was waiting up for you all night.
I should get going.
Hold on. I'm just gonna say hello.
You should stay with Yun.
Yun's like this because of me.
What do you mean?
I met someone else.
It just happened...
What... What did you do to Yun?
I'm not sure myself.
Kang Minju!
I really don't know.
I'm really not sure how we got into this mess.
Get out.
Get lost!
I'm sorry, Yun.
I had no idea what you were going through.
I didn't know it was bad enough for you to want to die.
Open the door. Please!
Minju! Open the door!
Kang Minju. Who's that guy next to you?
Who's that bastard next to you?
Do you wanna sleep with me?
If you get involved with me,
it'd be till death do us part.
I love you.
It just happened that way. I love you.
To some, love is as easy to spit out
as chewing gum.
But others will put their life on the line
for that person.
Think of it as being punished for your sins, lady.
This is #2204.
I'd like to rent out my apartment.
[Bank accounts: Kim Galchi / Yun Seo-kyeong]
Mr. Song.
He wouldn't take our Yun as well right?
Yun's all I've got.
He's my everything.
He wouldn't take him from me right?
Of course not.
If he was alive, he would be 27 years old by now.
That child who died unable to see the light of day
would be 27 by now.
I was counting the days without knowing.
If he hadn't died, today would be his birthday.
- 24.
25.
- 26.
- Six.
27.
Wait. Since you and Uncle are twins,
it's his birthday, too.
- Mom, let's call Uncle.
- OKay.
And Eunchae.
Let's call Eunchae, too.
Uncle!
Hurry up!
We even got a cake!
We got a delicious cake!
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
♪ Happy birthday, dear Mom and Uncle ♪
Hey, you!
- And Mom!
- No!
Hold her!
27 years ago,
a young actress fell in love with
a married man, some director.
She gave birth to twins.
I'll get going.
But the twins were given to an orphanage.
Maybe because they were afraid of the scandal.
Who cared what happened to the kids?
She had to make a living.
So one of them got adopted by an Australian couple.
But soon got abandoned by that family
and lived like a dog on the streets.
The other went looking for her mom
when she was five, got hit by a car
and became mentally disabled.
She remained a child, mentally.
Now, she lives with a fatherless son.
Truth will prevail in the end.
The ancient scholars were so wise...
How did they create such words of wisdom?
Who are you?
You've grown old as well.
27 years ago, I was a young reporter.
I saw you in front of the orphanage with the twins.
You can't fool the hands of time.
Oh, yeah. I asked Eunchae to come.
Oh, yeah. We asked her to come.
- But she didn't pick up.
- Nope!
- I want to see Eunchae.
- Me, too.
Where is Eunchae?
Where is she?
That child who died unable to see the light of day
would be 27 by now.
Do you know that guy?
Yes. He's like a brother to me.
Truth will prevail in the end.
The two kissed without taking a breath, then fainted.
Hey! Eunchae!
Mom, I can't believe this!
Yun wouldn't let go of Eunchae's hand.
I'm serious!
Eunchae can't even go to the bathroom!
That punk holds her hand even when he's asleep!
I'm serious!
She wants you on the phone
because she thinks I'm lying.
What mom doesn't believe her daughter?
Yeah, Mom. Sukchae's telling the truth.
Even the nurses are amazed.
Yun won't let go of Eunchae's hand!
When she tries to move away,
his heart rate spikes, so she can't.
There is a medical term for this psychological state.
The nurse said it was... something...
Of course not! She can't eat!
She can barely go to the bathroom.
What are you doing?
Eunchae!
What's wrong? Are you in pain?
- Are you okay?
- It doesn't hurt.
Minchae! Choi Yun is in the papers again.
[Choi Yun Overcoming His Car Accident Through Singing!]
Thanks to all your concerns,
my injuries are healing
and my wounds are improving.
You shouldn't be doing this right now.
I hope you're okay.
Are you okay, Yun?
I don't have to worry, right, son?
Where is he? He's not answering my calls.
Is he sleeping?
Yun. I'll be right back.
I'm going to get something from the car.
- Eunchae!
- Yeah?
There's somewhere you and I have to go to together.
Isn't it pretty? Isn't it just like you?
What is this?
It's your car now.
Huh?
- Pay for it with this.
- Yes, sir.
- Yun!
- Full payment, please.
Yes, sir. Thank you.
Wait! We're not buying this.
- Please proceed.
- Yes, sir.
Will you drive me around till I get better?
You know that my license is suspended
and I can't drive.
But still. I can't accept this, Yun.
It's always been heartbreaking to
see you struggle as you carried
all the clothes and equipment.
I'm okay. I'm strong. You know that.
And I need to get tougher anyways.
What's with you?
I've been your coordinator for long enough.
You never said anything before.
Why are you doing this now?
I was too wrapped up in that girl
to see what was in front of me.
She blinded me,
so I couldn't see what was happening.
I couldn't see how hard things were for you.
I'm sorry it took me so long.
Can we drive it out of here?
[5 missed calls from Song Eunchae]
I know your evil plan! You act all nice
but actually you're planning
to give me double the work, right?
Not only the coordinator but now I'm your driver, too?
You've only become more devious since the accident.
Fine, I'll take it, I suppose.
I've devoted so much time to you.
That's worth at least this.
You're dead meat if you try to take it back.
Stop. What are you doing?
Your hand saved me.
During the accident...
I was thinking, "So this is how I die.
I guess this is the end."
Then suddenly, I heard your voice.
"It's okay, Yun. It's going to be okay.
Don't go anywhere. Don't listen to anything.
Just hold my hand tight.
It's okay, Yun. It's nothing."
I'm never going to let go ever again.
Keep driving. I'll answer it.
It's Muhyeok.
Yeah, Muhyeok.
Eunchae is with me.
You can go home.
I cancelled everything today
so I can go on a date with Eunchae.
I'm...
I'm dating Eunchae.
Surprised, my Eunchae?
Yun.
Don't question the past.
Just forgive everything I've done.
I didn't know much back then.
Without you, I was like a lost child.
When you ate something and really enjoyed it,
I felt better than if I had eaten it myself.
How was I supposed to know that was love?
Yun.
I love you, Eunchae.
I'm sorry for realizing it so late.
I have to call my dad.
Wait for a bit.
I'm going to ask him to drive you home.
Hey!
Eunchae!
You sold the condo and moved here?
I've been thinking hard, Mr. Kang.
Or should I say, Cha Muhyeok?
I just don't get you.
Who are you, really?
Does it have something to do with Yun?
Do you have a grudge against Yun?
Because of you, I lost Yun and Eunchae,
the only people in my life who really loved me...
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I could just tell Yun.
I could tell him everything.
Do whatever you want.
Tell Yun that you got seduced
by his bastard manager.
Should I also tell him that I'm
still being seduced by that bastard?
Without you, I was like a lost child.
When you ate something and really enjoyed it,
I felt better than if I had eaten it myself.
How was I supposed to know that was love?
- Do you like me too?
- No!
Then why poke a man minding his own business?
Even if I, the girl of your dreams,
gets a little hurt, keep your cool.
Give me...
Give me a hug.
Like with Yun. Just one hug.
Don't go, Eunchae.
I won't burden you.
Don't go.
Yun is alive?
He's looking for you.
Put me down!
Would you rather eat or kiss me?
Would you rather eat or sleep with me?
I'm going to open the door and jump out!
Would you rather eat? Or just live with me?
Would you rather eat? Or would you rather...
die with me?
Could you take care of my sister and Galchi?
Mister!
Mister...
[Episode 10 Preview]
The increasingly painful headaches, the nosebleeds...
Do those mean I haven't got much time left?
[Sorry, I now await a beautiful death]
Was it a hard life?
No, because I knew I'd be back here some day
to find my birth mother who was
too poor to raise her child
and wanted to buy her a house.
Because I had hope, it wasn't hard at all.
[Love, I can no longer stop]
I can't forget Muhyeok.
I worry so much that Muhyeok might be
sad and lonely because of me.